{
  "name": "Maths times tables 1 to 4",
  "uniqueid": "607b56aa-a995-4412-9285-3215ec4ef253",
  "enabled": true,
  "questions": [
    {
      "questionText": "1 x 1",
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "1 x 2",
      "answer": "2"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "1 x 3",
      "answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "1 x 4",
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "1 x 5",
      "answer": "5"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "1 x 6",
      "answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "1 x 7",
      "answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "1 x 8",
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "1 x 9",
      "answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "1 x 10",
      "answer": "10"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "1 x 11",
      "answer": "11"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "1 x 12",
      "answer": "12"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "2 x 1",
      "answer": "2"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "2 x 2",
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "2 x 3",
      "answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "2 x 4",
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "2 x 5",
      "answer": "10"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "2 x 6",
      "answer": "12"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "2 x 7",
      "answer": "14"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "2 x 8",
      "answer": "16"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "2 x 9",
      "answer": "18"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "2 x 10",
      "answer": "20"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "2 x 11",
      "answer": "22"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "2 x 12",
      "answer": "24"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "3 x 1",
      "answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "3 x 2",
      "answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "3 x 3",
      "answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "3 x 4",
      "answer": "12"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "3 x 5",
      "answer": "15"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "3 x 6",
      "answer": "18"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "3 x 7",
      "answer": "21"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "3 x 8",
      "answer": "24"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "3 x 9",
      "answer": "27"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "3 x 10",
      "answer": "30"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "3 x 11",
      "answer": "33"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "3 x 12",
      "answer": "36"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "4 x 1",
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "4 x 2",
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "4 x 3",
      "answer": "12"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "4 x 4",
      "answer": "16"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "4 x 5",
      "answer": "20"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "4 x 6",
      "answer": "24"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "4 x 7",
      "answer": "28"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "4 x 8",
      "answer": "32"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "4 x 9",
      "answer": "36"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "4 x 10",
      "answer": "40"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "4 x 11",
      "answer": "44"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "4 x 12",
      "answer": "48"
    }
  ],
  "rules": {
    "questionsPerGame": 10,
    "answerAlternatives": "11223344556677889900",
    "answerButtonLimit": 5
  },
  "metadata": {
    "targetAges": [
      5,
      6
    ]
  }
}